dreamdth.com 2019-12-21

# Privacy Policy | DreamDTH

#### Who we are

DreamDTH is a fast growing news publication which covers news related to Direct To Home (DTH), Cable TV, IPTV, OTT, Telecom & Gadgets. Our website is at https://dreamdth.com.

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

#### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

#### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

#### Contact details

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, our contact details can be found on our [contact us page](https://dreamdth.com/contact/).

#### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you visit our login page, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

#### Advertising partners

This post confirms my ownership of the site and that this site adheres to Google AdSense program policies and Terms and Conditions. Third party vendors, including [Google](https://policies.google.com/?hl=en), use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website. Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the [ads preference manager](https://adssettings.google.com/). You can also opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).

#### **Analytics**

We use [Google Analytics](https://marketingplatform.google.com/about/analytics/) to calculate site metrics. This allows us to determine how people are using the site and improve it. 

#### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

#### How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see or edit their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

#### Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

#### How we protect your data

We are committed to ensuring that any information you provide to us is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable measures and procedures to safeguard and secure the information that we collect.

#### Acceptance of this policy

Continued use of our site signifies your acceptance of this policy. If you do not accept the policy then please do not use this site. When registering we will further request your explicit acceptance of the privacy policy.

#### Changes to this policy

We may make changes to this policy at any time. You may be asked to review and re-accept the information in this policy if it changes in the future.
